Hello everyone!
I am KANAMI, the Governor of KANAMI!
Oni shase!
This is Chunan KANAMI!
So, today I'd like to introduce you to some of my recent purchases from Grail!
Today, I'd like to introduce you to my recent purchase of Grail products!
Yay!
Okay, well, let's get right to it.
I've already got some summer clothes.
I'll introduce them to you all!
Let's get started!
Okay, let's get started!
First of all, here they are!
Here it is!
I'm wearing it right now!
Isn't it cute?
It's a little frilly here.
And white at the end.
It's cute.
You can see a little bit here.
Back and front.
I heard it doesn't matter which side is in the front or the back.
I heard it's okay to have this side in the back.
I thought it's cute to show a little skin here.
I thought it was cute.
I tried it on with this side in the front.
It has a little floral pattern.
It's cute.
It's nice.
White tends to get dirty easily.
And it's reasonably priced.
I thought it would be nice to have a few.
I bought it.
I think it's cute and a little girly.
I think it's a cute, slightly girly top.
Okay, next.
Here we go again.
White again!
I got some white pants.
Here they are.
And here they are.
Look at this.
Oh, no.
They're open. They're open like this. I really wanted pants like these.
They're all the rage these days, but you can get them at reasonable prices from Grail, so I thought it'd be nice to buy something a little more trendy at a reasonable price.
I thought it would be nice to buy something affordable that's a little trendy.
I'd like to enjoy summer's skinny-dipping. The interior is in. It's cute.
It's cool. It's summer.
Here.
I bought the set-up.
It was so cheap.
This one.
I wanted brown pants.
They're kind of amazing.
The fabric is a little satin-like.
It's very luxurious.
I bought them in mocha.
It's a little bit...
It's a calm color.
Not black.
Not white.
I wanted a different color.
I wanted pants in a different color.
I bought them.
It's a shirt set-up like this, but with a slightly shorter length.
I think it would be cute with a light top like this one.
And speaking of summer...
Speaking of summer...
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm? Yes, a yukata! I got a yukata too.
I found a cute yukata at Grail and bought it!
Ta-da!
It's made of a white base fabric
and the obi is pink.
Isn't it so cute?
I'm so glad I bought it because it's so cute!
And this yukata was only about 5,000 yen!
I thought it was really cheap, so I thought I'd have some fun with the accessories, so I bought this one.
I bought this belt with sparkles on it.
I bought a belt with glitter on it and put it on over the obi.
I'm going to put on a pearl accessory and make it pretty, and a little bit of everything else.
I bought this yukata at a reasonable price, so I'd like to arrange it in various ways that I don't usually do.
I'm going to make a yukata to my liking.
Please look forward to it!
I'll definitely post it again somewhere.
I'll definitely post it somewhere.
I've always wanted to wear a yukata with this lace design.
But I always have a hard time deciding what to do with it.
Also, it's usually a little bit later in the summer.
I often find myself wishing I had a yukata.
And sometimes I can't buy it because it's sold out.
I've never worn it before, so I got it right away in May.
I got it right away in May.
I'm so glad it's still in stock!
I'm really, really looking forward to wearing it!
I have this image of wearing it to
I'm going to Disney Sea
I want to take this Leena Belle-chan with me, so
I would like to wear a Leena Belle-chan catsuit
I'm looking forward to it!
It's going to be a cute outfit.I'm going to dress in a cute way.
I don't care about my age or anything, I just want to dress the way I want to dress.
I'd like to go to Disney Sea.
plus one or two other things
I bought a few things.
I'd like to show you what I bought.
Please look forward to it!
Here are some of Grail's purchases!
How was everyone's shopping experience?
Summer clothes are starting to arrive and I'm really looking forward to it.
I hope you all have fun with your outfits! Thank you very much for watching this week's show.
I hope you will subscribe to my channel and click the "Good" button.
Please subscribe to our channel!
See you next time!
See you soon!
Bye, bye, bye!
I'm an old person, I'm sorry.
Let's go!
ma ah ah ah ah ah ah
Sta.
귖
fortable
Subscribe to our channel!